Stacey Onayiga

stacey.fatunbi@gmail.com • linkedin/in/stacey-onayiga • Washington, DC • 763.412.9000

Senior Scientific Technical Writer

Meticulous and collaborative senior technical writer experienced in developing high quality technical content to clearly and efficiently explain highly complex data, systems, processes and products for information technology, biotechnology, and medical device industries. Recognized for understanding and translating complicated information for target audiences, content creation, attention to detail, project management, and strong communication skills.

Technical Skills:

Dreamweaver Python Oxygen XML Editor Vasont **Epic Medical Records System** DITA Notepad++ Madcap Flare Microsoft Office Suite GitHub SharePoint Adobe Creative Suite Sourcetree FrameMaker Jira Agile scrum methodology InDesign HTML/CSS Vscode Illustrator

Career Experience

Technical Writer, Amazon Pharmacy, Arlington, VA

Markdown

2022 to Present

Supported and refined the information management system for Pillpack related documentation used across Amazon Pharmacy fulfillment sites nation-wide.

- Overhauled and standardized internal process documentation for pharmacists and technicians on the Pillpack fulfillment floor.
- Successfully converted majority of SJIs to xml metalanguage in Q3 through Q4, reaching an approximate 70% completion rate of all Pillpack SJIs. This achievement allowed for single-sourcing of information and better content reuse to promote consistency within documented processes
- Streamline internal packaging and fulfillment process by vetting existing process paths in conjunction with associated documentation in order to reduce medical related errors/events (MREs), and other issues as it relates to packaging and fulfillment of medications for Amazon Pharmacy patients.
- Generated a standard service level agreement (SLA) to create procedural documents for Pillpack fulfillment to build trust with stakeholders in regards to creating and delivering on documentation related requests in a timely manner while adhering to scope and projected deadlines.
- Planned and coordinated initiative to enhance Runbook documentation for better reference and searchability; Created 'new and improved' exemplar to pilot developer and IT support issues.
- Partnered with stakeholders throughout Amazon Pharmacy Services to support initiatives to elevate, standardize, and host Amazon Pharmacy documentation across Rx Billing, Rx Integrity, and Rx Acquisition departments.

Stacey Onayiga

Page 2

- Collaborated with software development engineers (SDEs) within Amazon Pharmacy tech teams to bar raise, identify gaps, and formalize API documentation.
- Self-taught on fundamentals of good API documentation through personalized research and collaboration with SDEs to identify pain points of current API content and how APIs could be better utilized by the customer.
- Mentored writing colleagues on the basics of good API documentation and how to successfully write for APIs.

Technical Writer- Medical/Clinical, Amazon Laboratories, Arlington, VA

2020 to 2022

Generated and formalized procedural documentation for scientists and laboratory technicians to safely conduct SAR-COV-2 in-house test results through the use of Saliva Direct TM test methods.

- Collaborated with key stakeholders to globalize and standardize clinical processes, where feasible, across laboratory sites nation-wide.
- Bar-raised and refined quality policy guidelines to outline good documentation practices as it relates to creating, formatting, revising and version control of laboratory documents.
- Implemented strategies to ensure protocols and procedures maintained a level of quality and version control as it went through the documentation lifecycle process.
- Joined forces with other writer colleagues to develop a unique information architecture system to manage clinical documentation and testing protocols utilized by laboratory personnel.
- Drove efforts with on-site clinicians, compliance, and quality stakeholders to ensure laboratory related documentation adhered to the highest level of CLIA and CAP regulatory standards.

Technical Writer, Medtronic, Fridley, MN

2014 to 2020

Originated and designed clear, concise instructional materials for the safe and proper use of life-saving products and therapies for the nationally recognized Medtronic Restorative Therapies Group.

- Created New Product Introduction (NPI) programmer app labeling as lead technical writer for clinician
 and patient software platforms for Pelvic Health InterStim therapy; a breakthrough smartphone
 commercial-off-the-shelf application that allows for enhanced clinician programming capabilities and
 discreet patient use of a Medtronic device
- Mentored and lead technical writing team members through internal initiatives to enhance current processes and practice efficiencies
- Lead design phase reviews for labeling product deliverables and generate labeling according to intended use of product
- Developed labeling product requirements to drive robust and comprehensive labeling for target audiences
- Strictly adhered to federal, international regulations and industry labeling standards driven by FDA and TUV regulatory bodies
- Lead project meetings to convey labeling development status, inter-dependencies, production issues, and timeline impacts
- Initiated and implemented department objectives to standardize ISO symbol use for product labeling

Stacey Onayiga

Page | 3

Technical Writer, Digi International, Minnetonka, MN

2011 to 2014

Shifted career toward a passion for communication, bringing clarity and accuracy to creating technical documents and manuals, explaining complex information in a clear and concise manner, and working with scientific staff to ensure accuracy of product descriptions.

- Self-education on HTML/CSS programming; translated pdf manuals into new, interactive HTML content
- Generated XML/HTML-based web content for XBee cellular modems
- Built Quick Start guides for Connectcore gateway

Certified Nursing Assistant, Mercy Hospital, Coon Rapids, MN

2008 to 2011

Honored to provide intimate, hands-on healthcare to patients in psychiatric, intensive care, women & children's, cardiac catheter laboratory, surgical, and cardiac units.

- Established rapport and trust with patients and staff
- Held responsibility for monitoring vital signs, administering tests and medication, patient test and equipment preparation, charting patient records, and assisting nursing staff.

Personal Care Attendant, Relieve Care, Inc., Coon Rapids, MN

2006 to 2008

Compassionately served as a lifeline for adults with a variety of mental illnesses, helping them complete basic daily routines and develop a deeper sense of independence and quality of life.

- Ensured client health through meal preparation and food intake monitoring
- Accurately administered client's daily medications
- Coordinated community involvement activities

Education

Master of Arts in Health and Human Services Administration

St. Mary's University, Twin Cities, MN

Bachelor of Science in Science and Technical Communication

University of Minnesota – Twin Cities, MN

Certified Nursing Assistant

Nursing Assistant/Home Health Aide Certification, Brooklyn Park, MN Hennepin Technical College